Grigorii Sukhorukov

Nouvelle-Aquitaine, France



grsukhorukov@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/grigorii-sukhorukov-060067115

Summary

I began my bioinformatic career as an evolutionary biologist and continued it as a NGS specialist and deep learning engineer. On the way to my PhD I am quickly gaining confidence in solving complex and unorthodox problems effectively.

Experience



Bioinformatics Engineer

The Bordeaux Bioinformatics Center

Oct 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

Deep learning for novel virus detection in plants



>>> Intern

Statandocs

Mar 2019 - Apr 2019 (2 months)

Data analysis of clinical trials



M&S Decisions

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018 (3 months)

Meta-analysis and methodology study for mechanistic and semi-mechanistic modeling of primary and secondary endpoints in Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease (COPD)

Education



Université de Bordeaux

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Bioinformatics 2019 - 2022



Skolkovo Institute of Science and Technology

Master's degree, Bioinformatics 2017 - 2019



Lomonosov Moscow State University (MSU)

Bachelor's degree, Materials Science 2013 - 2017



1543

Licenses & Certifications

Deep Learning Specialization - Coursera
CAFQ5LLR9VQD

Machine Learning Foundations: A Case Study Approach - Coursera P243S3F9KQGS

Skills

Bioinformatics • Python • Deep Learning • Machine Learning • Research • Statistics • Bash • TensorFlow • Ray • Docker